你那客户很古怪吗
Is your client erratic?
我的  怎么这么说
My... Why?
他说这个叫埃尔斯贝特的
He says this Elsbeth has, uh,
表现得有些古怪
been demonstrating some erratic behavior,
他们不得不先做个心理评估
and they have to do a psych evaluation
才能转送她
before they can transport her.
责任问题嘛
Liability.
许多事情我都可以搞定
Well, I can trump a lot of things,
防范措施什么的就不行了
but I can't trump insurance issues,
你就去告诉你客户让她把心理评估过了
so you tell your client to pass her psych eval
我再提她上来
and I'll get her up here.
几小时后我们应该可以把埃尔斯贝特弄出来
We think we can get Elsbeth out in a few hours,
但眼下这次听证只能我负责
but I'll have to take this for now.
他们就打算在这里举行听证吗
They're going to do the hearing here?
这是仲裁员在这么短的时间里
It's the only place the arbitrators could find